They awakened a monster.
Nazi Supersoldier is a horror, action, science
fiction film directed by Ahmed Chaer.
A group of journalism students ventures into a remote forest and awakens a
long-frozen World War II experiment a superhuman Nazi soldier.
Hunted through cursed woods where trust crumbles and survival is
slim, they soon learn that some sins demand blood.
Juso, played by Erkan Sulcani.
Dennis, played by Linus Gomolka.
Felix, played by Roman Boeer de Garcez.
Idris, played by Leontin Slavkov.
Sarah, played by Antonia Catharina Düwel.
Sophia, played by Leah Herold.
A super soldier or supersoldier, is a concept soldier capable of operating beyond normal human abilities, usually
through permanent artificial enhancements such as genetic modification or technological integration.
The super soldier has been a common trope in science fiction and superhero fiction since the mid-20th century, but it's also
used in contemporary discussion of future military human enhancement (often with dystopian connotations).
The film explores themes of world war ii, woods, super
soldier, iron mask, secret laboratory.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.